Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications, 1944-2014 MS2374
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographic material and paper records, Series 1
  - Prints, Series 1 Subseries 2
    - A-3 Divided Levels, November 1955 - September 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 3)
    - A-4 Overpasses, Underpasses, August 1954 - May 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 4)
    - A-5 High and Low Traffic Density, July 1958; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 5)
    - A-6 Bridges, December 1931 - April 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 6)
    - A-7 Highways, Expressways, August 1952 - March 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 7)
    - A-8 Lane Marking and Discipline, May 1957 - June 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 8)
    - A-9 Roadside Service Facilities, Gas Stations, Telephones, Restaurants, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 9)
    - A-10 Pedestrian Facilities, Sidewalks, Crossings, Bridges, August 1953 - July 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 10)
    - A-11 Median Strips, Street Planning, Railings, Curbs, Details, etc., June 1952 - June 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 11)
    - A-12 Road Signs (Traffic Directions, Historic Sites, etc.), July 1955 - April 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 12)
    - A-13 Expressway Terminals, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 13)
    - A-14 Toll Stops, May 1959 - June 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 14)
    - A-15 Heliports, July 1958 - December 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73A, Folder 15)
    - B. Rail Transport, June 1955 - November 1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 1)
    - B-1 Relationship of Rails to Expressways, May 1955 - June 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 2)
    - B-2 Railbeds and Rolling Stock, 1950's - 1960's; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 3)
    - B-3 Stations, December 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 4)
    - B-4 Platforms and In-Transit Facilities, February 1956 - March 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 5)
    - B-5 Transfer Stations, Rubber to Rail, etc., January 1957 - April 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 6)
    - B-6 Monorail, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 7)
    - C. Bus Transit, January 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 8)
    - C-1 Stations, February 1951 - February 1959; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 9)
    - C-2 In Transit Facilities, May 1963; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 10)
    - D-1 Surface and Underground, November 1952 - July 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, October 1948 - September 1961; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73B, Folder 12)
    - Stations A-B, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Stations C's, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Stations D-E, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Stations F's, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Stations G, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Stations H-L, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Stations M-N, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Stations P-R, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Tabloid [1 of 2], 1980s; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Tabloid [2 of 2], 1980s; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Tabloid, June 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Tabloid, October 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Tabloid, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Tabloid, May 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - 10th Anniversary Book, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Construction of Metro, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Weiss Presentation, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous B+W Prints, pre-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Transit Schedules for Memorial Day Holiday, May 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Metro Magazine, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous B+W Prints, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous B+W Prints, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Metro Magazine, April 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - FY Budget Book, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Full Set of Station Maps, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous B+W Prints, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Photographs of Gude and Gordon Visit to TEC, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Prints for 25th Anniversary Book, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Slides Duplicates - 25th Anniversary Book, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Station Art - Atlanta, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Station Art - Chicago, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Station Art - Miami, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Station Art - San Francisco, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Dodge, Brig. Gen. Roy T. - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107A, Folder 1)
    - Egbert, John - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107A, Folder 2)
    - Lutz, Theodore - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107A, Folder 3)
    - McCarter, Walter J. - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107A, Folder 4)
    - Page, Richard - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107A, Folder 5)
    - Page, Richard S. - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107B, Folder 1)
    - Reuter, Lawrence G. - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107B, Folder 2)
    - Turner, Carmen E. - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107B, Folder 3)
    - Quenstedt, Warren - Bio, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 107B, Folder 4)
    - Addison Road to Army Navy Club, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Ballston to Bethesda, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Bicycle Racks to Brookland, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - C-11 to Chillum, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Dupont Circle to Eastern Market, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower Ave to Forest Glen, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Fan Shaft to Federal Center, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Federal City College, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Huntington to I-66, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Misc Arlington Photographs, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109A, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109A, Folder 2)
    - Sweden - Stockholm Prints, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109A, Folder 3)
    - Misc Prints/ Associated Documents [1 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109B, Folder 3)
    - Misc Prints/ Associated Documents [2 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110A, Folder 1)
    - Misc Prints/ Associated Documents [3 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110A, Folder 2)
    - Misc Prints/ Memos, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110A, Folder 3)
    - Photo Album, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110B, Folder 1)
      Areas include: Connecticut and K, Dupont Circle, Judiciary Square, Michigan Ave, Riggs Road, Porter Street, Takoma Park, Rhode Island Ave, Union Station, Van Ness, 12th and G streets, 18th and I streets, 23rd and I streets, Fine Arts Presentation Sept. 1967, 15th and I streets, Plaster Model, Color Renderings
  - Contact sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Contact Sheets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Contact Sheets, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Contact Sheets, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Contact Sheets, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Contact Sheets, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Contact Sheets, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15C, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15C, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 15C, Folder 3)
    - Unlabeled Proof Sheets, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16A, Folder 1)
    - TPAs 1, 1992-1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16A, Folder 2)
    - TPAs 2, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16A, Folder 3)
    - TPAs 3, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16A, Folder 4)
    - TPAs 4, 1995-2002; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, 2000-2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 16B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1982 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1982 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19A, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1985 [1of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1985 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1986 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1986 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 19B, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1982 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1982 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1982 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1982 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 20B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1982 [1 of 1]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1982 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 58B, Folder 7)
    - Portraits, 1980-1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23A, Folder 1)
    - Portraits, 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23A, Folder 2)
    - Portraits, 1983-1986 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23A, Folder 3)
    - Portraits, 1983-1986 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23A, Folder 4)
    - Portraits, 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23A, Folder 5)
    - Portraits, 1989-1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23A, Folder 6)
    - Portraits, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23B, Folder 1)
    - Portraits, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23B, Folder 2)
    - Portraits, 1995-1998 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23B, Folder 3)
    - Portraits, 1995-1998 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 23B, Folder 4)
    - Portraits, March 1974 - August 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 24A, Folder 1)
    - Portraits, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 24A, Folder 2)
    - Portraits, January 1980 - September 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 24A, Folder 3)
    - Board Members, 1971, 1972, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24A, Folder 4)
    - Board Members, 1974; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24A, Folder 5)
    - Board Members, 1975 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24B, Folder 1)
    - Board Members, 1975 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24B, Folder 2)
    - Board Members, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24B, Folder 3)
    - Board Members, 1970s - 1990s; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24B, Folder 4)
    - Board Members, 1970s - 1990s; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24B, Folder 5)
    - Board Members, 1970s - 1990s; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27C, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1984 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27C, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1984 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27C, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27C, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 27C, Folder 5)
    - Portraits, 1998 - 1999 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28C, Folder 4)
    - Portraits, 1998 - 1999 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28C, Folder 5)
    - Portraits, 2000s [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28C, Folder 6)
    - Portraits, 2000s [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 28C, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1993; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Contact Sheets, November 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Contact Sheets, January 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1986 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1986 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1986 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1986 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, July 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, August 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 32B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, December 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, January - February 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, May - June 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, July - August 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, September 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33A, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, October 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, November - December 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, February 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, March 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, April 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, May 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, June 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 33B, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, November 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, December 2000; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, January 2001 [1 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets, January 2001 [2 of 2]; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 47B, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, February 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets, March 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets, April 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, May 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 4)
    - Contact Sheets, June 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 5)
    - Contact Sheets, July 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets, August 2001; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 38A, Folder 7)